<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://jabrantesradiology.github.io/RadBlog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://jabrantesradiology.github.io/RadBlog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-12-29T08:41:55-06:00</updated><id>https://jabrantesradiology.github.io/RadBlog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">DataRad - A blog where Radiology, Data Science and all things AI get together!</title><subtitle>This blog cover topics such as the latest advances in medical imaging, the use of machine learning and artificial intelligence in healthcare, and the role of data science in improving patient outcomes. Whether you are a medical professional, a data scientist, or simply interested in these fields, we hope you will find this blog both informative and engaging. Thank you for visiting!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Discovering the Cutting-Edge of Medical AI: A Series on the RSNA Deep Learning Lab 2022</title><link href="https://jabrantesradiology.github.io/RadBlog/fastpages/jupyter/2022/12/28/deep_learning_intro.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Discovering the Cutting-Edge of Medical AI: A Series on the RSNA Deep Learning Lab 2022" /><published>2022-12-28T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2022-12-28T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>https://jabrantesradiology.github.io/RadBlog/fastpages/jupyter/2022/12/28/deep_learning_intro</id><author><name></name></author><category term="fastpages" /><category term="jupyter" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[This blog post serves as an introduction to a series of posts about the Radiological Society of North America's (RSNA) annual meeting and its session on AI, machine learning, and deep learning applied to radiology and medicine. The post provides an overview of the RSNA annual meeting, including its history and significance as a scientific society, and summarizes the main themes and ideas presented during the session on AI and machine learning. The post also includes links to the relevant code and resources on the RSNA GitHub repository and encourages readers to follow along with the series for more in-depth coverage of the topics discussed.]]></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://jabrantesradiology.github.io/RadBlog/images/image1.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://jabrantesradiology.github.io/RadBlog/images/image1.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>